<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Digital Memory</title><link>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/</link><description>Recent content on Digital Memory</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>crucial conversations</title><link>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/crucial-conversations/highlights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/crucial-conversations/highlights/</guid><description>Book: Crucial Conversations # Crucial Conversation krimage shel kän´vŭr sa´ shen) n A discussion between two or more people where (1) stakes are high, (2) opinions vary, and (3) emotions run strong.</description></item><item><title>learning-go</title><link>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/learning-go/highlights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/learning-go/highlights/</guid><description>Go Run -&amp;gt; Use go run when you want to treat a Go program like a script and run the source code immediately. Go Build -&amp;gt; build a binary for later use
Getting Third-Party Go Tools # Go’s method for publishing code is a bit different than most other languages. Go developers don’t rely on a centrally hosted service, like Maven Central for Java or the NPM registry for JavaScript. Instead, they share projects via their source code repositories.</description></item><item><title>With ToC</title><link>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/with-toc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/with-toc/</guid><description>Caput vino delphine in tamen vias # Cognita laeva illo fracta # Lorem markdownum pavent auras, surgit nunc cingentibus libet Laomedonque que est. Pastor An arbor filia foedat, ne fugit aliter, per. Helicona illas et callida neptem est Oresitrophos caput, dentibus est venit. Tenet reddite famuli praesentem fortibus, quaeque vis foret si frondes gelidos gravidae circumtulit inpulit armenta nativum.
Te at cruciabere vides rubentis manebo Maturuit in praetemptat ruborem ignara postquam habitasse Subitarum supplevit quoque fontesque venabula spretis modo Montis tot est mali quasque gravis Quinquennem domus arsit ipse Pellem turis pugnabant locavit Natus quaerere # Pectora et sine mulcere, coniuge dum tincta incurvae.</description></item><item><title>Kubernetes in Action</title><link>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/kubernetes-in-action/highlights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/kubernetes-in-action/highlights/</guid><description>Book: Kubernetes in Action # Chapter 1 # Difference between Virtual Machines and Containers # Using VMs to isolate groups of applications vs. isolating individual apps with containers:
When you run three VMs on a host, you have three completely separate operating systems running on and sharing the same bare-metal hardware. Underneath those VMs is the host’s OS and a hypervisor, which divides the physical hardware resources into smaller sets of virtual resources that can be used by the operating system inside each VM.</description></item><item><title>Without ToC</title><link>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/without-toc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://paulocdf.github.io/digital-memory/docs/example/table-of-contents/without-toc/</guid><description>At me ipso nepotibus nunc celebratior genus # Tanto oblite # Lorem markdownum pectora novis patenti igne sua opus aurae feras materiaque illic demersit imago et aristas questaque posset. Vomit quoque suo inhaesuro clara. Esse cumque, per referri triste. Ut exponit solisque communis in tendens vincetis agisque iamque huic bene ante vetat omina Thebae rates. Aeacus servat admonitu concidit, ad resimas vultus et rugas vultu dignamque Siphnon.
Quam iugulum regia simulacra, plus meruit humo pecorumque haesit, ab discedunt dixit: ritu pharetramque.</description></item></channel></rss>